University of Arizona Agricultural Experiment Station records, 1890-1915
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VI: Financial Records, 1913-1915
  - Financial Correspondence: State Entomologist. 1913-1915 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
  - Financial Correspondence: U. S. D. A. Office of Experiment Stations, Irrigation Investigations. 1914-1915 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence: U. S. Geological Survey, Water Resources Branch. 1914-1915 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Correspondence. 1913-1915 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Records. 1913-1915 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Financial Correspondence: Prescott Dry Farm, L. L. Bates. 1913-1915 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Financial Correspondence: Snowflake Dry Farm, Don C. Smith, etc. 1914-1915 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Financial Correspondence: Sulphur Spring Dry Farm, C. R. Fillerup. 1914-1915 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Financial Correspondence: Morse, Stanley F., Acting Agriculturalist. 1913-1914 (Box 28, Folder 13)